1. Easy to distinguish a piece of work: grp associated, picture of it, creator
2. Easy to see if it's been updated since you last viewed it
<!-- 3. Easy to see if anyone is currently viewing it right now. -->



OUR SCHEDULE

Feed finished (end of Wed)
Fix view for when you click (Thurs)
On Friday complete Eugene version

login, hook-up to parse, fix bugs

Wed get Charles
Wed get Casie & Marina

Ongoing:
	- use it with girl
- find 2 people in the same class









BUGS
1. remains blue photo button if touch and drag outside
2. double tap
3. instead of turning blue, graying out or enlarging or wiggling
4. nsinternalinconsistencyexception failed to determine navigation directino for scroll

ADD ONS
1. alert view needs some altering visually (look at fb photo)
2. should you be alterted if...
....a) have shit in post comment field and then click away which would consequently delete the currently selected box
....b) click x to exit feedback view should alert if there exists at least one dotbox with at least 1 comment
....c) if you x a dotbox that has a comment then should you be alerted



FUTURE ADD ONS
- create bounds around the buttons
- figure out a better button then the x for exit button feedback mode
- don't have overlapping dotboxes

Future Testing
0. Do we need more of a way to look at the overview of everything you have done?
1. Should you add a box when you dismiss tutorial alert?
2. Should you create bounds around the buttons?
3. "tap where you want feedback" how does this feel? >>>>

(Pieter and co)
People don't know you can leave boxes (not dots or something)
and that you can do this multiple places

4. Is is strange that a box is added when you zoom in/out?

FUTURE FUTURE ADD ONS:
- flash
- focus
- filters
- rotation
- mark as complete





Serena

<!-- 1. fix height resizing -->
<!-- 2. make into constants
 --><!-- 1. you have to be able to create deeper comments with elipsis
 --><!-- 2. should go into full from full in comment mode -->
<!-- 3. remove flash -- 0 comments to first ??? what should animation be? -->
1. Make into UITextView instead of UILabel which should fix height shit on table cell.
2. be able to highlight text in table view
4. animate the textfield
5. fix labels in post comment
6. be able to highlight text in tableview
7. cutting off lines in post comment
8. add ellipsis
9. deleting shouldn't be so easy
10. fix so that resizing is more proper and less jankalicious

Hani
1. shouldn't be able to put box handles off screen



2) individual converastion - fix views so that creator privlages, different colors (1 days)
3) nice looking feed view + indiviual conversation (2-3 days)
4) login page make pretty (1 days)
5) extra time to make speed + aethetically pleasing + fix bugs (2-3 days)

B. network + groups (Friday Morning)
C. adding images to comment thread & making them into scroll views
D. navagation of boxes
