BIG "T" to do List
A. hook up to back end
- color is different based on new box or old box

B. logo + design

C. notification list

D. network + groups (Friday Morning)

E. landscape mode should work

F. having multiple images and figuring out what that means

G. create filters: created by me, all, by group, by recency, by trending (these should be determined based on testing)

H. navagation of boxes use < > arrow








OPEN QUESTIONS
1. Organizer
- documents one after each other in organizer will look too similar and be hard to distinguish if they are the same
2. What is the best way to mark homework?
- handles getting clumsy for dotboxes
- kind of wihs she coudl drag over the region
- wanted to highlight soemthing within region
- highlight and draw

ORGANIZER
1. Easy to distinguish a piece of work: grp associated, picture of it, creator
2. Easy to see if it's been updated since you last viewed it

QUESTION TO ASK DURING TESTING
0. Do we need more of a way to look at the overview of everything you have done?
1. "tap where you want feedback" how does this feel? >>>>
-> coding excersise didn't make sense with this message

(Pieter and co)
People don't know you can leave boxes (not dots or something)
and that you can do this multiple places

2. Should it be more explicit to dimiss keyboard?  Should you have reverse swip gesture on keyboard?












HANI FUTURE
1. shouldn't be able to put box handles off screen
2. don't allow the dotbox to resize and have the icons switch around
3. no overlapping dotboxes
4. create bounds around icons on feedpack page so you can't put dotbox there
5. you should add a dotbox when you dimiss tutorial alert

MOST IMPORTANT CHANGES
2. change swipe gesture recognizer on organizer to swipe to correct view and swipe on navigation should swipe to last selected view or not do anything
3. should you be alterted if...
....a) have shit in post comment field and then click away which would consequently delete the currently selected box
....b) click x to exit feedback view should alert if there exists at least one dotbox with at least 1 comment
....c) if you x a dotbox that has a comment then should you be alerted
....e) if you spend time resizing and moving dotbox the should be alerted if you delete it

VISUAL CHANGES
0. whenever you add a new sheet by clicking plane button, have organizer very obviously add it or show changes.
1. alert view needs some altering visually (look at fb photo)
2. buttons colors. remains blue photo button if touch and drag outside, instead of turning blue, graying out or enlarging or wiggling
3. figure out a better button then the x for exit button feedback mode
4. the sign up screen
- once you navigate to a log in or sign up screen, have the button only appear when you are there
- problem is log in looks relaly plain as a button
- underline sign up button
5. post comment container and table comments
- mess around with styling for post comment container
- table handle top should be changing arrow
- animate post field
- change to instagram like view on feed
6. add consistent shadows across and create file of uibutton stuff

BUGS
0. got to tap too many times on the take photo button to take photo on camera
1. double tap should not leave dotbox
2. touch down on white x and then move finger away (but dont' lift up), it one time froze the swipe to other pages features and in general doesn't unselect.

FUTURE ADD-ONS
1. change camera take photo button to be similar to pintrist in aethetics and functionality
2. add tilt feature on newsfeed
2.5 add tilt feature to x and paper planes icon on feedback view controller
3. mark diff items in organizer as complete
4. long hold on organizer item shows last comment or something
5. flash, focus, and rotation for camera
6. filters for hw
7. ability to reverse camera



HARD BUGS
1. Doesn't seem like it's caused by the tranistion method in PageViewController since when you try to catch it, nothing is logged.
- tried limiting clicks
- tried having a boolean
- tried dispatching it asychronously to the main queue

2014-07-17 09:24:29.508 PaperPlanesV0.2.0[7788:60b] *** Assertion failure in -[_UIQueuingScrollView _didScrollWithAnimation:force:], /SourceCache/UIKit/UIKit-2935.137/_UIQueuingScrollView.m:799
2014-07-17 09:24:29.511 PaperPlanesV0.2.0[7788:60b] *** Terminating app due to uncaught exception 'NSInternalInconsistencyException', reason: 'Failed to determine navigation direction for scroll'
*** First throw call stack:
(0x2e347fd3 0x38bc0ccf 0x2e347ead 0x2ecf4d5b 0x310c7bfd 0x310c7851 0x310c4309 0x30d07483 0x30d06e6d 0x30d06d4d 0x3082fdf3 0x3082fb9d 0x335fc75d 0x2f032451 0x2e307ef9 0x2e312ab7 0x2e312a53 0x2e311227 0x2e27bf0f 0x2e27bcf3 0x331d4663 0x30bc716d 0x4e625 0x390cdab7)
libc++abi.dylib: terminating with uncaught exception of type NSException
